One love can change your life.
I Still Believe is a music, drama, romance film directed by Andrew Erwin.
The true-life story of Christian music star Jeremy Camp and his journey of
love and loss that looks to prove there is always hope.
Jeremy Camp, played by KJ Apa.
Melissa Henning, played by Britt Robertson.
Jean-Luc Lajoie, played by Nathan Parsons.
Tom Camp, played by Gary Sinise.
Terry Camp, played by Shania Twain.
Josh Camp, played by Reuben Dodd.
I Still Believe is a 2020 American biographical Christian romantic drama film directed by the Erwin
brothers and starring KJ Apa, Britt Robertson, Shania Twain, Melissa Roxburgh, and Gary Sinise.
It is based on the life of American contemporary Christian music singer-songwriter Jeremy Camp and his first
wife, Melissa Lynn Henning-Camp, who was diagnosed with ovarian cancer shortly before they married.
Camp's song "I Still Believe" is the film's namesake.
The film is the first production by Kingdom Story Company, the Erwin Brothers' fifth
feature film, and their second to be released under the Lionsgate banner.
It premiered at ArcLight Hollywood on March 7, 2020, and was
theatrically released in the United States on March 13, 2020.
It received mixed reviews from critics, who commended the film for depicting faith
in the midst of suffering, but criticized the plot and characters.
Lionsgate released the film to video on demand on March
27, 2020, due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
The film explores themes of biography, romance, christian film, true story.
The tone is emotional.